

Muhammad Alimie

Software Developer



014-715 9204



muhdalimie@gmail.com



Sungai Buloh, Selangor



linkedin.com/in/muhammadalimie



alimierosli.github.io/portfolio

About Me

software an experienced developer with a strong focus on frontend development. While I have hands-on exposure to full-stack technologies, my passion lies in building responsive, accessible, and user-friendly interfaces.

₩ Skills

- · Angular, React, Vuejs
- Bootstrap, Tailwind
- Git Control Version
- Nodejs Nestjs
- AWS, GCP
- .Net MVC & Razor (FE)
- Java Spring Boot
- PHP Laravel
- MySQL, Postgresql



Education

Bachelors Degree Computer Science (Mutimedia Computing) Universiti Teknologi MARA - UITM

Graduated in September 2018 with a CGPA of 3.32. Achieved strong results in programming courses. Developed a native Android app for mobile data security using Java for the final year project.

Matriculation Certificate

Johor Matriculation College

2013 - 2014

Completed Pure Science matriculation with a CGPA of 3.22. Studied Chemistry, Physics, Biology, and Mathematics. Served as a Committee Member for Community Service and Class Practicum.

Experience

Senior Software Developer

Agmo Studio Sdn Bhd

2021 - Now

- Progressively promoted from E1 to E2, and then to Software Engineer (SE) level.
- Appointed as Assistant Team Lead
- Developed frontend applications with Angular, React.js, and Vue.js, turning UI/UX designs into responsive websites
- Developed REST API using NestJS and PostgreSQL
- Experienced working with AWS & GCP
- Involved in integrating complex external plugins/third party services such as 2c2p, Data One & eKYC
- Built REST APIs on AWS Lambda using the Serverless Framework and Infrastructure as Code (IaC)
- Appointed as Tech Lead for multiple projects, providing technical solutions
- Collaborate with Solution Architect on infrastructure design and best practices

2019 - 2020

Software Engineer

MIMOS Berhad

- Contributed to the development of the Food Safety System Malaysia (FoSIM) for the Ministry of Health (KKM) - fosim.moh.gov.my
- Handled backend development with Java Spring Boot and frontend development with Angular.
- Designed and managed MySQL databases for assigned modules.

2018 - 2019

Software Engineer

Datakraf Solution Sdn Bhd

- Developed full-stack modules using PHP (Laravel MVC) and MySQL
- Developed Human Resource Management System (HRMS) using PHP Laravel for Syarikat Air Darul Aman (SADA)
- Integrated payment gateways (iPay88, FPX) into payment systems.
- Managed cloud and hosting using DigitalOcean droplets, NginX, Apache2 and CloudFlare

References

Teh Sang Khai

Agmo Studio / Team Lead

Phone: 016-594 1817

Email: skteh@agmostudio.com

Razak Khir

MIMOS / Supervisor

Phone: 017-356 7662

Email: razak.khir77@gmail.com